inobscuro.com 2016-05-13

# Privacy | In obscuro

This privacy policy sets out how the website inObscuro (inobscuro.com) uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from December 30, 2015.

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

## Your personal information

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

Specifically, we are using this information for:

  * Analytics
  * Interaction with external social networks and platforms
  * Managing email addresses and sending messages
  * Contact forms

The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through this Application and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the website owner of all responsibility.

### Contact form

If you choose to use a Contact form or Request form to contact me directly, this information will never be publicly displayed, given away or sold to a third party. It will only be used to reply back to your message.

### Newsletter subscription

When you voluntarily subscribe to my e-mail newsletter, **you agree to share the information you provided in the form with the e-mail service MailChimp**.

This information is only used to send you e-mails to which you agreed to receive. These e-mails include information on free and premium graphic resources published on this website.

**You can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of every e-mail**.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards. We do not use an SSL certificate.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

If you disable cookies, it will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

The following are not Strictly Necessary, but are required to provide you with the best user experience and also to tell us which pages you find most interesting (anonymously).

### Functional Cookies

This Website Will:

  * Track the pages you visits via Google Analytics
  * Create a cookie if you switch the website language, to remember your language preference

### Targeting Cookies

This Website Will:

  * Allow you to share pages with social networks such as Facebook, Twitter, etc.
  * Serve Google AdSense ads based on your interests

We use third party advertisements on inobscuro.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

### DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

## Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act

According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

  * Users can visit our site anonymously
  * Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
  * Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes: On our Privacy Policy Page
  * Users are able to change their personal information: By emailing us

### How does our site handle do not track signals?

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

### Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?

It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking.

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

  * We will notify the users via email within 7 business days
  * We will notify the users via in site notification within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:

  * NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
  * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

## Contact us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

inObscuro  
Markovici 15  
Rijeka 51000  
Croatia  
nelchee@inobscuro.com

Last edited on: December 30, 2015
